Guide to the Tuol Sleng confessions and photographs, 1991-1993
Tuol Sleng confessions and photographs, 1991-1993
- Series III: Confessions O-T
  - Names: S
    - Names: So
      - Sok Ngim, N/A (Reel 159, Frame 2)
        Dates of Confessions: 18/7/1976(2); 19/7/1976; 10/7/1976; 25/7/1976; 2/8/1976; 5/8/1976; 17/8/1976
      - Sok Nguon, N/A (Reel 140, Frame 5)
        Dates of Confessions: 20/1/1977; 21/1/1977
      - Sok Nhanh, 15/11/1975 (Reel 156, Frame 8)
      - Sok Nhean, N/A (Reel 140, Frame 2)
      - Sok Nith, 17/10/1977 (Reel 155, Frame 24)
        Dates of Confessions: 17/10/1977
      - Sok Noeurn, 3/1977 (Reel 150, Frame 19)
        Dates of Confessions: 5/3/1977
      - Sok Oeurn, N/A (Reel 143, Frame 1)
        Dates of Confessions: 2/9/1976(2); 6/9/1976(2); 8/9/1976(2); 9/9/1976; 10/8/1976; 10/9/1976; 11/9/1976(2); 12/9/1976; 13/9/1976; 18/9/1976; 20/9/1976; 22/9/1976; 14/3/1977
        29/3/1977; 22/4/1977; 18/5/1977; 24/5/1977
      - Sok Pak, 23/5/1977 (Reel 155, Frame 23)
      - Sok Phal, 3/1977/ (Reel 142, Frame 12)
        Dates of Confessions: 1/4/1977; 19/4/1977
      - Sok Phean, 24/5/1978 (Reel 141, Frame 16)
        Dates of Confessions: 30/5/1978; 2/6/1978
      - Sok Phom, 17/7/1978 (Reel 133, Frame 6)
      - Sok Phum, 17/7/1978 (Reel 155, Frame 15)
      - Sok Ra, 6/3/1978 (Reel 153, Frame 1)
      - Sok Saim, N/A (Reel 156, Frame 26)
        Dates of Confessions: 31/7/1977
      - Sok Sak, 12/6/1977 (Reel 151, Frame 19)
        Dates of Confessions: 19/9/1977
      - Sok Sam Ol, 15/3/1977 (Reel 152, Frame 8)
        Dates of Confessions: 20/4/1977; 21/4/1977
      - Sok Sam On, N/A (Reel 155, Frame 5)
        Dates of Confessions: 4/1/1977; 10/4/1977; 22/4/1977
      - Sok Samoeurn, N/A (Reel 145, Frame 6)
        Dates of Confessions: 14/1/1977; 4/3/1977(18); 28/2/1977; 1/3/1977(3); 2/3/1977(16); 4/3/1977(18); 5/3/1977(12); 6/3/1977(2); 7/3/1977(10)
      - Sok Sang, N/A (Reel 156, Frame 19)
      - Sok Sarith, 28/8/1978 (Reel 151, Frame 35)
      - Sok Seang, N/A (Reel 154, Frame 2)
        Dates of Confessions: 15/1/1978
      - Sok Sem, 9/1/1978 (Reel 144, Frame 11)
      - Sok Sem, 5/3/1978 (Reel 153, Frame 3)
        Dates of Confessions: 17/3/1978; 10/3/1978
      - Sok Sin, N/A (Reel 139, Frame 6)
      - Sok Snguon, 2/10/1977 (Reel 146, Frame 12)
        Dates of Confessions: 29/11/1977
      - Sok Soeurn, N/A (Reel 158, Frame 15)
      - Sok Sokhom, 26/2/1978 (Reel 156, Frame 9)
        Dates of Confessions: 5/3/1993
      - Sok Song, N/A (Reel 158, Frame 5)
      - Sok Song Vat, 5/3/1978 (Reel 144, Frame 10)
        Dates of Confessions: 17/3/1978; one section undated
      - Sok Sorth, 19/6/1976 (Reel N/A, Frame N/A)
        Dates of Confessions: 18/7/1976; 26/7/1976(2); 6/8/1976(2); 18/9/1977(10); 22/9/1976; 24/9/1977; 62 sections undated
      - Sok Sry, 10/12/1978 (Reel 160, Frame 3)
      - Sok Sun Ny, N/A (Reel 139, Frame 13)
      - Sok To Sivanna, 11/3/1978 (Reel 154, Frame 40)
        Dates of Confessions: 15/3/1978
      - Sok Tum, 7/8/1977 (Reel 146, Frame 15)
      - Sok Vorak, 23/11/1977 (Reel 159, Frame 21)
      - Sok Yan, N/A (Reel 142, Frame 1)
        Dates of Confessions: 22/9/1976; 8/10/1976; 22/9/1976
      - Sok Yean, 28/8/1977 (Reel 134, Frame 2)
        Dates of Confessions: 18/9/1977; 19/9/1977
      - Sok Yim, N/A (Reel 141, Frame 5)
        Dates of Confessions: 24/11/1976; 25/11/1976; 27/11/1976(3); 28/11/1976(3); 6/12/1976(7); 8/12/1976(3); 10/12/1976(3); 27/12/1976; 28/12/1976(5); 1/1/1977; 3/1/1977; 23/1/1977(3)
      - Sok Yorn, N/A (Reel 146, Frame 17)
      - Sok Yun, 27/3/1978 (Reel 156, Frame 18)
        Dates of Confessions: 12/6/1978(2); 6/8/1978
      - Sok Yuth, N/A (Reel 158, Frame 18)
        Dates of Confessions: 20/1/1977; 26/1/1977(2); 4/2/1977; 6/2/1977; 11/2/1977(3); 13/2/1977; 16/2/1977
      - Som Chan, 9/3/1978 (Reel 144, Frame 2)
      - Som Chea, 15/3/1978 (Reel 142, Frame 2)
        Dates of Confessions: 28/3/1978; 7/5/1978; 25/5/1978(2)
      - Som Chheav, 26/6/1978 (Reel 142, Frame 9)
        Dates of Confessions: 4/7/1978; 25/7/1978
      - Som Dang, 27/7/1977 (Reel 156, Frame 23)
        Dates of Confessions: 6/8/1977; 15/9/1977
      - Som Doeum, N/A (Reel 149, Frame 4)
        Dates of Confessions: 9/1975; 6/9/1975
      - Som Dou, 20/1/1977 (Reel 157, Frame 8)
        Dates of Confessions: 13/2/1977; 14/2/1977(2); 16/2/1977; 12/2/1977; 18/2/1977
      - Som Hok Sreng, N/A (Reel 152, Frame 4)
      - Som Koeurn, N/A (Reel 141, Frame 7)
      - Som Lorn, 29/3/1977 (Reel 155, Frame 14)
      - Som Ly, N/A (Reel 150, Frame 5)
        Dates of Confessions: 19/4/1977
      - Som Meng, 30/8/1977 (Reel 147, Frame 8)
      - Som Neng, 25/10/1976 (Reel 143, Frame 5)
        Dates of Confessions: 24/11/1976; 25/11/1976; 31/11/1976; 3/12/1976; 8/12/1976; 9/12/1976; 12/12/1976; 9/2/1977
      - Som Neou, N/A (Reel 157, Frame 4)
      - Som Oeurn, 8/2/1978 (Reel 159, Frame 26)
      - Som Oung, N/A (Reel 137, Frame 5)
        Dates of Confessions: 26/6/1976; 10/7/1976; 13/7/1976(2); 24/7/1976(2); 15/7/1976; 16/7/1976; 17/6/1977; 18/7/1976; 20/7/1976; 22/7/1976; 23/7/1976; 29/7/1976; 4/1976; 6 sections undated
      - Som Phon, 25/1/1978 (Reel 159, Frame 8)
      - Som Rom, N/A (Reel 151, Frame 9)
      - Som Sakhan, 23/9/1976 (Reel 153, Frame 7)
        Dates of Confessions: 2/1/1977; 17/9/1977
      - Som Sam Ul, 25/3/1978 (Reel 153, Frame 10)
        Dates of Confessions: 27/3/1978(2); 28/3/1978
      - Som Samoeurn, 19/6/1977 (Reel 147, Frame 13)
        Dates of Confessions: 7/7/1977; 13/10/1977
      - Som Sang, N/A (Reel 129, Frame 4)
        Dates of Confessions: 11/7/1976; 12/7/1976; 13/7/1976(2); 6/7/1976; 14/7/1976; 15/7/1976; 18/7/1976; 19/7/1976; 20/7/1976; 6/8/1976(2); 14/8/1976; 18/7/1976(2); 21/8/1976; 24/8/1976; 28/7/1976; 4 sections undated
      - Som Sarin, 22/1/1976 (Reel 135, Frame 15)
      - Som Say, N/A (Reel 158, Frame 4)
      - Som Seila, 20/3/1977 (Reel 145, Frame 7)
        Dates of Confessions: 11/4/1977; 12/4/1977(2); 13/4/1977; 16/4/1977(2); 18/4/1977(2); 19/4/1977(3); 20/4/1977((2); 21/4/1977(2); 22/4/1977(5); 23/4/1977(3); 24/4/1977(3); 25/4/1977(2); 26/4/1977(3)
        27/4/1977(2); 28/4/1977(4); 29/4/1977; 30/4/1977(3); 31/4/1977; 1/5/1977(5)
        2/5/1977(3); 3/5/1977(4); 9/5/1977(4); 5/5/1977
      - Som Song Heang, 12/9/1975 (Reel 143, Frame 2)
        Dates of Confessions: 22/9/1975
      - Som Than, N/A (Reel 142, Frame 4)
      - Som Thim, N/A (Reel 143, Frame 6)
        Dates of Confessions: 20/2/1977; 23/2/1977; 24/2/1977; 25/2/1977(2); 26/2/1977; 1/3/1977; 2/3/1977; 3/3/1977; 4/3/1977; 27/12/1977; 18/12/1977
      - Som Torn, N/A (Reel 151, Frame 16)
      - Som Yat, N/A (Reel 139, Frame 11)
      - Som Yong, 26/8/1975 (Reel 152, Frame 6)
      - Son Mrak, 1/1978 (Reel 152, Frame 25)
      - Son San, N/A (Reel 151, Frame 11)
        Age: 14
        Dates of Confessions: 7/8/1976
      - Song Hak, N/A (Reel 155, Frame 8)
      - Song Ly, N/A (Reel 146, Frame 9)
      - Soom Sioon Chharieng (Chharteng), 6/9/1975 (Reel 185, Frame 43)
      - Soomboun Setbopha, 6/9/1975 (Reel 185, Frame 44)
        Nationality (if foreign): Taing Island
      - Sophann Pa Vong Sa, 6/9/1975 (Reel 185, Frame 42)
      - Sophat, N/A (Reel 135, Frame 4)
        Dates of Confessions: 22/6/1976
      - Sophon, N/A (Reel 136, Frame 18)
      - Sor Seng Ly, 23/1/1977 (Reel 156, Frame 24)
      - Sor Tong Ly, 27/5/1977 (Reel 144, Frame 7)
        Dates of Confessions: 29/7/1977; 18/10/1977; 24/10/1977
      - Sorn Oeung, N/A (Reel 149, Frame 17)
      - Sorn San, N/A (Reel 151, Frame 14)
      - Sorn Sao, N/A (Reel 155, Frame 11)
        Dates of Confessions: 7/10/1976; 10/1/0/1976; 16/10/1976; 15/11/1976; 7/11/1976; 10/11/1976; 11/1976; 4/1976
      - Sorng Bunsy, 7/7/1978 (Reel 152, Frame 1)
      - Sos Khoeurn, N/A (Reel 139, Frame 16)
      - Sos Tort, N/A (Reel 157, Frame 20)
        Dates of Confessions: 19/2/1977
      - Sot Chhorn, N/A (Reel 157, Frame 23)
        Dates of Confessions: 23/9/1976; 5/10/1976; 10/11/1976
      - Sot Kry, 1/7/1978 (Reel 156, Frame 13)
      - Sot Sean, N/A (Reel 132, Frame 2)
      - Sot Souk, 25/11/1977 (Reel 131, Frame 1)
        Dates of Confessions: 9/2/1978; 2 sections undated
      - Sota Pros Reno, 21/12/1975 (Reel 185, Frame 46)
        Nationality (if foreign): Kong Island
      - Soth Chhorn, N/A (Reel 149, Frame 20)
        Dates of Confessions: 23/9/1976
      - Sou Born, 10/8/1977 (Reel 135, Frame 8)
        Dates of Confessions: 1/11/1977; 5/11/1977; 11/10/1977
      - Sou Chak, N/A (Reel 157, Frame 18)
      - Sou Chim, 28/6/1977 (Reel 155, Frame 22)
      - Sou Heang, 6/7/1978 (Reel 151, Frame 32)
        Dates of Confessions: 18/7/1978
      - Sou Lichheng, N/A (Reel 138, Frame 8)
        Dates of Confessions: 7/12/1976
      - Sou Nem, 1/10/1975 (Reel 140, Frame 9)
      - Sou Neou, N/A (Reel 142, Frame 8)
        Dates of Confessions: 19/6/1977(2); 20/6/1977; 26/6/1977; 24/7/1977; 10/8/1977
      - Sou Peou, N/A (Reel 135, Frame 3)
      - Sou Phun Phay, N/A (Reel 150, Frame 12)
      - Sou Rom, N/A (Reel 154, Frame 34)
      - Sou San, 25/9/1977 (Reel 130, Frame 10)
        Dates of Confessions: 25/12/1977; 13/12/1977; 28/9/1977; 16/10/1977
      - Sou Say, N/A (Reel 158, Frame 9)
        Dates of Confessions: 2/11/1976; 3/11/1976(2); 4/11/1976; 6/11/1976; 7/11//1976(2); 8/11/1976(2);2/11/1976(4)
      - Sou Tuon, 28/6/1977 (Reel 155, Frame 21)
        Dates of Confessions: 3/6/1977; 17/6/1977
      - Sou Vann, N/A (Reel 130, Frame 16)
      - Souk Hoeurn, 3/9/1977 (Reel 141, Frame 1)
        Age: 68
      - Souk Sak, 12/6/1977 (Reel 131, Frame 7)
      - Soun Kaset, N/A (Reel 159, Frame 12)
      - Soun Long, 29/2/1976 (Reel 152, Frame 34)
      - Soung Phay, 1/1/1976 (Reel 153, Frame 8)
        Dates of Confessions: 24/2/1976
      - Sour Tha, 20/5/1977 (Reel 129, Frame 8)
      - Sov Horn, 17/7/1978 (Reel 158, Frame 9)
      - Sov Lan, N/A (Reel 149, Frame 23)
    - Names: Sr
      - Sray Pak, 16/10/1977 (Reel 136, Frame 10)
      - Sre, N/A (Reel 153, Frame 5)
      - Srea Seng Ly, 25/1/1978 (Reel 158, Frame 21)
      - Sream Lorn, N/A (Reel 154, Frame 4)
        Dates of Confessions: 20/7/1977
      - Sreang Seang Ly, 4/2/1978 (Reel 154, Frame 33)
      - Srei Bun Than, 21/8/1977 (Reel 148, Frame 14)
      - Sreng Chamroeurn, 24/3/1977 (Reel 135, Frame 14)
        Dates of Confessions: 4/6/1977; 20/8/1977
      - Sreng Tuch, 18/11/1975 (Reel 148, Frame 9)
        Dates of Confessions: 13/1/1976
      - Sreourng Lin, 1/1/1978 (Reel 134, Frame 4)
        Dates of Confessions: 3/2/1977(2)
      - Srev Ples, 10/1977 (Reel 137, Frame 11)
      - Srey At, 11/2/1978 (Reel 138, Frame 10)
      - Srey Bun Thoek, 1/8/1977 (Reel 135, Frame 10)
        Dates of Confessions: 24/9/1977; 25/10/1977
      - Srey Chham, 28/6/1978 (Reel 149, Frame 21)
        Dates of Confessions: 6/1978
      - Srey Chheang, N/A (Reel 133, Frame 1)
        Dates of Confessions: 13/11/1976; 3/12/1976; 5/12/1976; 8/12/1976(2); 16/12/1976; 19/12/1976; 21/12/1976; 4/1/1977; 10/1/1977; 13/1/1977; 6/12/1977(2); 1/12/1976; 4/12/1976
        4/12/1976; 11/12/1976; 17/12/1976; 20/12/1976; 30/12/1976; 3/1/1977
        11/1/1977(2); 25/2/1977; 5 sections undated
      - Srey Chhin, N/A (Reel 154, Frame 19)
      - Srey Daung, N/A (Reel 128, Frame 9)
      - Srey Dim, N/A (Reel 151, Frame 12)
      - Srey Koy, N/A (Reel 157, Frame 19)
      - Srey Kun, 12/6/1977 (Reel 151, Frame 20)
        Dates of Confessions: 17/9/1977; 15/11/1977
      - Srey Lam, N/A (Reel 150, Frame 3)
        Dates of Confessions: 1/3/1977; 2/3/1977(3); 24/2/1977(2); 28/2/1977; 26/2/1977
      - Srey Namm, N/A (Reel 150, Frame 8)
        Dates of Confessions: 2/9/1976
      - Srey Oeurn, 28/8/1977 (Reel 146, Frame 20)
        Dates of Confessions: 4/9/1978; 26/10/1977(2)
      - Srey Peng, 11/7/1976 (Reel 143, Frame 7)
      - Srey Phanarin, 7/12/1975 (Reel 134, Frame 8)
      - Srey Ren, N/A (Reel 143, Frame 16)
        Dates of Confessions: 5/1977
      - Srey Sambo, 2/2/1977 (Reel 136, Frame 7)
        Dates of Confessions: 7/5/1977; 10/6/1977
      - Srey Saroeurn, 3/10/1977 (Reel 137, Frame 3)
      - Srey Savuth, 25/3/1978 (Reel 158, Frame 1)
      - Srey Sithan, N/A (Reel 157, Frame 25)
        Dates of Confessions: 10/6/1976; 3/7/1976; 19/8/1976; 24/8/1976; 26/8/1976; 28/8/1976
      - Srey Sroy, N/A (Reel 157, Frame 13)
      - Srey Yan, 24/5/1978 (Reel 131, Frame 9)
        Dates of Confessions: 23/6/1978; 11/7/1978
      - Srey Yat, 20/10/1976 (Reel 149, Frame 19)
        Dates of Confessions: 6/2/1977(2)
      - Sri Naem Puraksi, 14/4/1976 (Reel 148, Frame 3)
      - Srin Samy, 1/1976 (Reel 149, Frame 9)
      - Srin Srea, N/A (Reel 129, Frame 7)
      - Sriv Leang, 6/10/1977 (Reel 131, Frame 8)
      - Sru, 6/1977 (Reel 148, Frame 11)
        Dates of Confessions: 7/11/1977; 3/11/1977
      - Srun Ly, N/A (Reel 137, Frame 7)
      - Srun Meng Chheang, 2/1/1976 (Reel 144, Frame 16)
      - Srun Seng H'At, 28/8/1977 (Reel 148, Frame 13)
      - Sruy Bun, N/A (Reel 154, Frame 30)
        Dates of Confessions: 6/2/1977; 17/1/1977
      - Sry Mab, N/A (Reel 146, Frame 5)
    - Names: Su-Sy
      - Su Chea, 13/3/1978 (Reel 149, Frame 5)
        Dates of Confessions: 25/3/1978(2); 6/4/1978; 22/3/1978; 4 sections undated
      - Suan Chreng, 3/10/1975 (Reel 151, Frame 39)
      - Suan Gim Jhun, 9/3/1977 (Reel 151, Frame 24)
      - Suan Khan, 11/7/1976 (Reel 145, Frame 5)
      - Suan San, 26/6/1977 (Reel 132, Frame 3)
        Dates of Confessions: 11//7/1977; 28/8/1977; 17/9/1977; 27/10/1977(2)
      - Suan San, 30/10/1977 (Reel 148, Frame 1)
        Dates of Confessions: 2/11/1977; 5/1/1979
      - Suan Sarroeurn, 13/7/1978 (Reel 128, Frame 5)
        Dates of Confessions: 10/7/1978; 2 sections undated
      - Suan Som, N/A (Reel 156, Frame 5)
      - Suar Sit, N/A (Reel 148, Frame 17)
      - Suas Jim, 27/3/1978 (Reel 151, Frame 8)
        Dates of Confessions: 18/5/1978
      - Suas Phon, 8/3/1978 (Reel 154, Frame 5)
        Dates of Confessions: 23/3/1978
      - Suas Phun, 18/11/1975 (Reel 156, Frame 11)
      - Suas Yan, 26/11/1975 (Reel 143, Frame 8)
      - Suen Seng, 13/6/1976 (Reel 150, Frame 9)
      - Suk Ouc, N/A (Reel 147, Frame 4)
        Dates of Confessions: 10/7/1976; 11/7/1976; 14/7/1976; 15/7/1976; 16/7/1976(2); 18/7/1976(2); 20/7/1976(2); 21/7/1976; 22/7/1976; 23/7/1976(3); 24/7/1976(3)
      - Suk Sunthal, N/A (Reel 149, Frame 8)
      - Sukh R""An, 9/1978 (Reel 147, Frame 2)
      - Sum Bhin, 25/5/1976 (Reel 147, Frame 17)
      - Sum Chhan, 9/7/1976 (Reel 143, Frame 9)
      - Sum Chheang, N/A (Reel 154, Frame 9)
      - Sum Chhum, 26/12/1977 (Reel 155, Frame 18)
        Dates of Confessions: 5/1/1977
      - Sum Kam Phon, N/A (Reel 129, Frame 3)
      - Sum Khan, 12/9/1976 (Reel 146, Frame 7)
        Dates of Confessions: 17/9/1976(2); 23/9/1976(3); 24/9/1976; 25/9/1976; 27/9/1976; 28/9/1976(3); 19/9/1976; 3/10/1976; 4/10/1976; 5/10/1976(3); 6/10/1976(2)
        8/10/1976(3); 9/10/96; 10/10/1976(2)
      - Sum Mao, 8/1977 (Reel 151, Frame 30)
      - Sum Nor, 12/10/1978 (Reel 130, Frame 4)
        Dates of Confessions: 26/10/1978
      - Sum Sam Oeurn, 2/10/1977 (Reel 149, Frame 11)
        Dates of Confessions: 17/12/1977
      - Sum Say, 6/1977 (Reel 134, Frame 7)
      - Sum Soeurng, N/A (Reel 129, Frame 12)
        Dates of Confessions: 6/7/67(3); 7/8/67(2); 2/8/67(2); 9/8/67(11); 11/8/67(3)
      - Sum Son, 25/9/1977 (Reel 130, Frame 13)
        Dates of Confessions: 17/11/1977; 18/11/1977
      - Sum Than, N/A (Reel 156, Frame 25)
      - Sum Tour, 27/9/1975 (Reel 157, Frame 1)
        Dates of Confessions: 3/12/1975
      - Sum You, 1/1/1978 (Reel 152, Frame 24)
      - Sun Born, N/A (Reel 150, Frame 1)
      - Sun Dan, N/A (Reel 153, Frame 12)
      - Sun Hoeurn, 6/7/1978 (Reel 136, Frame 14)
        Dates of Confessions: 26/8/1978
      - Sun Kun, 8/1977 (Reel 155, Frame 3)
        Dates of Confessions: 21/7/1977; 26/7/1977; 5/9/1977
      - Sun Luch, 3/7/1977 (Reel 139, Frame 7)
      - Sun Sat, 26/6/1976 (Reel 128, Frame 8)
        Dates of Confessions: 13/8/1976(18); 14/8/1976(5)
      - Sun Seak, 30/11/1978 (Reel 160, Frame 5)
      - Sun Sem, 10/12/1978 (Reel 160, Frame 1)
      - Sun Sroeurm, 12/1975 (Reel 149, Frame 2)
      - Sun Suy, N/A (Reel 143, Frame 13)
      - Sun Suy, N/A (Reel 152, Frame 28)
      - Sun Suy, N/A (Reel 152, Frame 38)
      - Sun Than, 2/1977 (Reel 149, Frame 6)
      - Sun Tim, 28/6/1977 (Reel 155, Frame 2)
      - Sun Touch, N/A (Reel 129, Frame 1)
        Dates of Confessions: 14/11/1976; 19/11/1976; 20/11/1976; 22/11/1976; 26/11/1976; 29/11/1976; 2/12/1976; 4/12/1976; 6/12/1976; 9/12/1976; 9/12/1976; 11/12/1976
        14/12/1976; 16/12/1976'; 18/12/1976; 20/12/1976
      - Sun Touch, 28/10/1976 (Reel 156, Frame 3)
        Dates of Confessions: 6/12/1976; 9/12/1976; 17/12/1976; 21/12/1976; 16/1/1977
      - Sun Ty, 10/12/1978 (Reel 159, Frame 11)
      - Sung Chheourng, 3/11/1977 (Reel 132, Frame 11)
      - Suoang Soeurng, N/A (Reel 145, Frame 2)
        Dates of Confessions: 4/11/1976; 5/11/1976(2); 10/11/1976; 12/11/1976; 13/11/1976; 14/11/1976; 15/11/1976; 16/11/1976; 17/11/1976; 18/11/1976; 19/11/1976
        20/11/1976; 21/11/1976; 23/11/1976;24/11/1976; 25/11/1976; 27/11/1976
        29/11/1976; 30/11/1976; 7/11/1976; 9/11/1976; 1/12/1976; 2/12/1976(2)
        3/12//1976;10/12/1976; 11/12/1976
      - Suom Phoeun, 23/12/1977 (Reel 154, Frame 25)
      - Suon Bun Thoeurn, N/A (Reel 159, Frame 18)
      - Suon Chan, 6/1/1976 (Reel 142, Frame 5)
        Dates of Confessions: 13/9/1976; 16/9/1976; 17/9/1976; 21/9/1976(2); 22/9/1976(3); 23/9/1976(3); 24/9/1976(2); 25/9/1976(10); 27/9/1976; 28/9/1976(3)
        29/9/1976(2); 30/9/1976(4); 10/1976/(3); 4/10/1976(2); 28/9/1976(3)
        29/9/1976(2); 30/9/1976(4); 1/10/1976(3); 4/10/1976(2)
      - Suon Chhaum, 15/9/1977 (Reel 135, Frame 13)
      - Suon Hoeurng, 16/3/1977 (Reel 128, Frame 6)
        Dates of Confessions: 26/8/1977; 12/9/1977
      - Suon Long, 29/2/1976 (Reel 152, Frame 34)
      - Suon Ol, 29/9/1977 (Reel 135, Frame 9)
      - Suon Sam, 8/8/1977 (Reel 140, Frame 6)
      - Suon Sem, 29/7/1977 (Reel 145, Frame 4)
        Dates of Confessions: 1/8/1977
      - Suon Sin, 20/8/1976 (Reel 141, Frame 6)
        Dates of Confessions: 2/10/1976(5); 15/10/1976(2); 16/10/1976(3); 17/10/1976; 18/10/1976(13); 20/10/1976(2)
      - Suon Soeurn, N/A (Reel 140, Frame 17)
      - Suon Sony, N/A (Reel 157, Frame 27)
        Dates of Confessions: 11/12/1975
      - Suon Sreng, 26/8/1975 (Reel 130, Frame 3)
      - Suong Chhay Leng, 25/8/1976 (Reel 145, Frame 15)
        Dates of Confessions: 5/10/1976; 10/10/1976
      - Suong Kem, 4/1977 (Reel 158, Frame 19)
      - Suong Lok, 16/3/1977 (Reel 152, Frame 31)
      - Suong Tong, 11/3/1977 (Reel 136, Frame 5)
        Dates of Confessions: 23/3/1977; 28/3/1977; 20/4/1977; 20/8/1977
      - Suong Yat, 15/5/1977 (Reel 159, Frame 25)
      - Suor Tith, 25/12/1976 (Reel 131, Frame 12)
        Dates of Confessions: 29/2/1976; 10/1/1977
      - Suos Neou, 31/8/1976 (Reel 132, Frame 4)
        Dates of Confessions: 19/1976; 29/1976; 3/9/1976; 4/9/1976; 5/9/1976; 6/9/1976(2); 7/9/1976; 8/9/1976;9/9/1976; 14/9/1976(2); 15/9/1976; 16/9/1976(2); 17/9/1976
        19/9/1976; 20/9/1976; 23/9/1976(2); 24/9/1976; 25/9/1976; 26/9/1976; 28/9/1976
        29/9/1976; 30/9/1976; 18/9/1976; 1/10/1976; 2/10/1976; 6/10/1976; 7/10/1976; 8/10/1976
      - Suos Sarom, 26/9/1977 (Reel 146, Frame 3)
      - Suos Seng, 11/1975 (Reel 139, Frame 9)
      - Suos Yan, 26/11/1975 (Reel 143, Frame 8)
      - Sut Jhyan, 24/6/1978 (Reel 148, Frame 8)
      - Suth On, 2/8/1977 (Reel 134, Frame 3)
        Dates of Confessions: 16/9/1977; 5/10/1977(2); 16/9/1977
      - Suth Sry, N/A (Reel 154, Frame 36)
      - Suy Chheng Huot, N/A (Reel 157, Frame 9)
      - Suy Khoeurn, 8/1977 (Reel 157, Frame 6)
        Dates of Confessions: 16/8/1977; 10/10/1977
      - Suy Koeut, N/A (Reel 152, Frame 23)
      - Suy Nat, 11/12/1976 (Reel 147, Frame 20)
        Dates of Confessions: 19/12/1976; 24/12/1976; 7/1/1977; 4/1/1977
      - Suy Phal, 28/4/1977 (Reel 128, Frame 4)
        Dates of Confessions: 22/1/1977; 15/5/1977; 1/7/1977; 30/6/1977; 17/6/1977; 6/8/1977; 29/10/1977; 8/7/1977
      - Suy Saroeurng, N/A (Reel 135, Frame 12)
      - Svaiiy Nounh, 29/11/1978 (Reel 147, Frame 5)
        Dates of Confessions: 3/12/1978; 22/12/1978
      - Svang Khom, 12/6/1978 (Reel 158, Frame 26)
      - Svay An, 30/7/1977 (Reel 129, Frame 11)
      - Svay Bory, 10/3/1978 (Reel 152, Frame 3)
        Dates of Confessions: 10/3/1978
      - Svay Chuong, 10/1976 (Reel 140, Frame 13)
      - Svay Khat, 7/4/1978 (Reel 154, Frame 14)
        Dates of Confessions: 15/4/1978; 17/4/1978
      - Svay Lonh, 2/1977 (Reel 140, Frame 1)
      - Svay Math, 15/3/1978 (Reel 154, Frame 6)
      - Svay Nak, 1/4/1977 (Reel 143, Frame 11)
      - Svay Rom, N/A (Reel 150, Frame 21)
      - Svay Sean, 7/1977 (Reel 146, Frame 14)
        Dates of Confessions: 25/8/1977; 20/9/1977; 7/9/1977
      - Svay Sim, 21/9/1977 (Reel 146, Frame 2)
      - Svay Soth, N/A (Reel 150, Frame 23)
      - Svay Yan, N/A (Reel 134, Frame 1)
        Dates of Confessions: 6/1/1976; 17/11/1976; 3/12/1976; 8/12/1976; 10/12/1976; 22/12/1976
      - Sy Lean An, 16/3/1978 (Reel 147, Frame 15)
        Dates of Confessions: 4/4/1978; 24/6/1978
      - Sy Ngeng, 18/1/1978 (Reel 137, Frame 8)
      - Syn Cuv, 20/9/1975 (Reel 148, Frame 12)
- Series IV. Confessions T-Y
  - Names: T
    - Ta Chi Veng, 11/1975 (Reel 175, Frame 15)
      Dates of Confessions: 22/11/1975
    - Taing An, 2/10/1977 (Reel 179, Frame 40)
      Age: 28 n
      Dates of Confessions: 21/1/0/1977; 31/10/1977
    - Taing Heap, N/A (Reel 169, Frame 13)
    - Taing Khet, N/A (Reel 168, Frame 11)
      Dates of Confessions: 21/10/1976; 23/12/1976; 25/10/1976; 27/10/1976(2); 28/10/1976
    - Taing Meng Hor, 30/3/1976 (Reel 173, Frame 1)
    - Taing Nogoc Tay, 24/1/1978 (Reel 186, Frame 36)
    - Taing Sam, N/A (Reel 178, Frame 10)
    - Taing Siv Leng, 17/11/1976 (Reel 167, Frame 9)
      Dates of Confessions: 14/12/1976; 27/11/1976; 22/11/1976; 17/12/1976; 3/12/1976; 29/11/1976; 28/11/1976; 21/11/1976; 19/12/1976; 18/12/1976
    - Taing Ul, 6/5/1976 (Reel 178, Frame 21)
      Dates of Confessions: 18/7/1976; 15/7/1976; 29/7/1976; 31/8/1976(4); 1/9/1976
    - Taing Vanasy, 1/9/1976 (Reel 180, Frame 12)
      Dates of Confessions: 15/9/1976; 14/9/1976; 6/9/1976; 10/9/1976; 14/9/1976
    - Taing Veng Seu, 19/4/1978 (Reel 168, Frame 8)
    - Tak Chhea, 2/1/1978 (Reel 180, Frame 8)
    - Tak Yean, 27/3/1977 (Reel 178, Frame 16)
    - Tan Doeurn, N/A (Reel 173, Frame 16)
    - Tan Leak Pheng, 12/11/1977 (Reel 177, Frame 6)
    - Tan Leam, 25/2/1978 (Reel 179, Frame 15)
    - Tan Pheng, N/A (Reel 173, Frame 5)
      Dates of Confessions: 1/3/1976(2); 24/2/1976
    - Tan Phoeurng, N/A (Reel 177, Frame 12)
    - Tan Yeng, 23/8/1977 (Reel 171, Frame 11)
      Dates of Confessions: 29/8/1977(2); 2/10/1977; 25/11/1977
    - Tann Chhay Heng, 16/5/1977 (Reel 178, Frame 22)
    - Tann Kim Tao, 25/5/1976 (Reel 174, Frame 9)
    - Tann Say, N/A (Reel 179, Frame 30)
    - Tann Sok Huoy, 26/2/1977 (Reel 178, Frame 14)
      Dates of Confessions: 3/4/1977
    - Tann Tith Leng, 20/5/1975 (Reel 179, Frame 32)
      Dates of Confessions: 20/5/1976
    - Tann Try, 17/2/1977 (Reel 168, Frame 1)
      Dates of Confessions: 19/4/1977; 27/4/1977; 8/5/1977; 30/6/1977(2); 11/5/1977; 17/5/1977
    - Tao Kim Huy, 20/8/1975 (Reel 172, Frame 15)
      Dates of Confessions: 14/9/1975
    - Tap Seap, N/A (Reel 169, Frame 20)
      Dates of Confessions: 2,12,15,18,20,22,25,28,30/11/1976; 8/12/1976(3); 6,7,4, 20/12/1976
    - Tat, N/A (Reel 171, Frame 9)
    - Tath Laysrin, 6/7/1978 (Reel 170, Frame 11)